Guide to the David B. McCall Papers, 1939-1999 and undated, bulk 1980-1994
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- McCaffrey & McCall Series (Includes C.J. Laroche & Co.), 1958-1992 and undated, (7 boxes)
  - Clients Subseries, 1964-1992 and undated
    - Pro Bono, Public Service and Nonprofit
      - New York Zoological Society
        - Donor lists, 1977-1978 and undated (Box 5)
        - Meetings, 1978-1984 (Box 5)
        - Solicitations, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
      - Save the Children
        - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 5)
        - Information package, Africa Emergency Fund, ca. 1986 (Box 5)
        - Pamphlet, Your Sponsored Child, ca. 1979 (Box 5)
        - Press package, 1985 (Box 6)
        - Public Information Division clippings collection, 1985 (Box 6)
        - Publication, Africa, Seeds of Hope, ca. 1986 (Box 6)
        - Publications, 1983-1985 (Box 6)
        - Reports, 1985 (Box 6)
      - Tobacco advertising controversy (See also Oversize Materials, Oversize Box OV3)
        - Excerpts from legislative testimony, undated (Box 6)
        - Final report, Tobacco Use in America Conference, 1989 (Box 6)
        - Hearings
          - House Subcommittee on Health and the Environment, 1986 (Box 6)
          - H.R. 1250, 1989 July 25 (Box 6)
        - Slides, undated (Box 6)
        - Supporting materials, 1987-1989 (Box 6)
      - Unsell the War
        - Conference report, 1971 (Box 6)
        - Correspondence, 1971, 1992 (Box 6)
      - Various charity work, 1967-1987 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda Subseries, 1960-1989 and undated
    - Benefits, 1973-1974 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1963, 1969-1987, (5 folders) (Box 7)
    - Council on Children, Media and Merchandising, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Memoranda
      - General, 1988-1989 (Box 7)
      - Relating to Charles Saatchi Museum, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Printed Materials Subseries, 1958-1990 and undated
    - Annual Report, 1969, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Appointment book with corporate logo, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Artwork and sketches, undated (Box 7)
    - Business cards and notepad with corporate logo, undated (Box 7)
    - Clippings and reprints, 1958-1990, (3 folders) (Box 7)
    - Creativity in Advertising brochures, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Directory, 1983 (Box 7)
    - House Organ, 1972-1975 (Box 7)
    - McCalendar, 1981-1990, (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - McNews, 1978 (Box 8)
    - Menu, dinner event, 1978 (Box 8)
    - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Royal Bruce's Wall Wisdom, undated (Box 8)
    - Saatchi Collection, 1987 (Box 8)
- Radio Stations Series, 1981-1991, (1 box)
  Includes correspondence, periodic reports and profit-and-loss statements for the 790 Communications Corporation and the 1340 Broadcasting Corporation, two radio broadcasting corporations in which McCaffrey & McCall had invested. McCall retained an interest in the corporations after his retirement from McCaffrey & McCall in 1987. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Board meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Financial reports, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Insurance, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Legal matters, 1983-1987 (Box 8)
  - Memoranda, 1981-1988 (Box 8)
  - Printed materials, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Profit and loss statements, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Proposed acquisitions, 1987-1991 (See also Oversize Materials, Oversize Box OV3.) (Box 8)
  - Stock shareholder materials, 1985-1988 (Box 8)
- Sawyer Miller Group (SMG) Series, 1989-1993 and undated, (9 boxes)
  Contains administrative records, correspondence and client files. Sawyer Miller, where McCall served as a partner from 1989 to 1993, was instrumental in helping the telecommunications industry after the breakup of the Bell system into regional operating companies. Other clients included the National Football League and the Puerto Rico Telephone Company, along with a number of political candidates such as Harvey Gannt of North Carolina and George Keverian of Massachusetts, and international leaders including Ramón Mitra (presidential candidate, Philippines) and Mario Vargas Llosa (presidential candidate, Peru). The series is organized into three subseries--Administrative Files, Clients, and Correspondence and Memoranda--and alphabetically therein.
  - Administrative Files Subseries, 1990-1993 and undated
    - Advertising and the Future, undated (Box 9)
    - Agents of Change, SMG mission statement, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Bozell benefits briefing materials, 1992-1993 (Box 9)
    - Clippings, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Corporate brochure, undated (Box 9)
    - Corporate credo, undated (Box 9)
    - Creative Department
      - Correspondence and general, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
      - Freelance writers, samples and correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 9)
      - Start-Work authorization forms, 1991 (Box 9)
    - David B. McCall, files pertaining directly to official activities at SMG
      - Department of Justice forms, 1992 (Box 9)
        Memo and Form CRM-156, to register as the representative of a foreign national. SMG performed public relations work for several foreign government agencies and companies.
      - Expenses, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
      - Notes on divisional luncheon, 1991 Oct. 7 (Box 9)
      - Travel
        - Itineraries, 1990 (Box 9)
        - Records, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
    - KRC Research (Division of SMG)
      - General, 1992 (Box 9)
      - Project process statement, 1990 (Box 9)
    - List of possible foundation names, undated (Box 9)
    - List of possible new TV channel names, ca. 1991 (Box 9)
    - Meetings
      - Managing Directors meeting, 1991 Jun. 3 (Box 9)
      - Partners meeting, 1990-1992
        - Business plan, 1990 (Box 9)
        - Financial statements, 1990 (Box 9)
        - Memoranda, 1990-1992 (Box 9)
        - Operating results, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Merger with Robinson, Lake, Lerrer & Montgomery (RLLM), 1993 (Box 9)
    - New York City restaurants, 1991 (Box 9)
      Includes clippings, guides and recommendations.
    - Partner biographies, undated (Box 10)
    - Personnel assignments and memoranda, 1990-1991 and undated (Box 10)
    - Phone listings, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
    - Plan for the 1990s, undated (Box 10)
    - Projects status reports, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Random Thoughts about Sawyer Miller at a Critical Juncture, undated (Box 10)
    - Resignation letters, 1992-1993 (Box 10)
    - Resumes, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
    - Thoughts of a CEO, undated (Box 10)
    - Timesheet and expense report information, 1993 (Box 10)
  - Clients Subseries, 1989-1993 and undated
    - Commercial (Box 10)
      - 20th Century Fund, 1991 (Box 10)
      - American Airlines, 1992-1993, (2 folders) (Box 10)
      - American Express, 1991 (Box 10)
      - Bahamas hospitality industry, memoranda and campaign strategy, 1990 (Box 10)
      - Barnes & Noble, 1991 (Box 10)
      - Bessemer Capital Partners, 1991 (Box 10)
      - Champion Mills, 1992 (Box 10)
      - Charter Medical, 1993 (Box 10)
      - CIT Group, 1991 (Box 10)
      - Dubow, Arthur, undated (Box 10)
        Business plan for a proposed periodical entitled Mercury.
      - Ecuador Tourist Promotion Office, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
      - Farmers Insurance Group, 1989 (Box 10)
      - Hertz, 1990 (Box 11)
      - Merck & Co., 1991 (Box 11)
      - Morgan Stanley, 1991 (Box 11)
      - National Football League, 1991 (Box 11)
      - New England Telephone, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 11)
      - Nissan Motor Corporation in the U.S., 1991 (Box 11)
      - Pirelli-Armstrong Tire Corporation, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
      - Pharmaceutical Manufacturers' Association (PMA), 1993 (Box 11)
      - Pizza Hut, 1991 (Box 11)
      - Progressive Insurance Company, 1988-1990 (Box 11)
      - Puerto Rico Telephone Company (PRTC), 1990 (See also Oversize Materials, Oversize Box OV3.), (2 folders) (Box 11)
      - Regional Bells
        - Advertising and media presentation, 1992 Dec. 21 (Box 11)
        - Advertising campaign, 1990 (Box 12)
        - Advertising strategy, 1990-1991 (See also Oversize Materials, Oversize Box OV3.), (4 folders) (Box 12)
        - Articles, 1990 (Box 12)
        - Bell Operating Companies, 1991 (Box 12)
        - Communications strategy report, 1992 June 11 (Box 12)
        - Creative campaign, 1993 (Box 12)
        - Focus groups, 1993 (Box 13)
        - Memoranda, 1990-1992, (4 folders) (Box 13)
        - New England Electric, 1992 (Box 13)
        - Research, 1990 (Box 13)
        - Television, 1992 (Box 13)
      - Sony Corporation of America, 1990 (Box 13)
      - Steel industry, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Political
      - Annaldo, Andrew, undated (Box 13)
        One-time candidate for Mayor of Providence, R.I.
      - Carlin, John, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 13)
        Candidate for Governor, Kan.
      - Clinton (William Jefferson) Presidential campaign, 1992-1993 (Box 13)
      - Colombian government, national image campaign, 1991 (Box 13)
      - Gannt, Harvey, 1990 (Box 14)
        Candidate for U.S. Senate, N.C.
      - Henry, Sherrye, 1990 (Box 14)
        Candidate for State Senate, N.Y.
      - Keverian, George, 1990, (3 folders) (Box 14)
        Former state Speaker of House; candidate for Commonwealth Treasurer, Mass.
      - Mitra, Ramón V., 1991 (Box 14)
        Candidate for Presidency, Philippines.
      - Murphy, Evelyn, 1990 (Box 14)
      - Social Democratic Party (SDP), Nigeria 1991 (Box 14)
        Article on Chairman Baba Gana Kingibe.
      - Solomon, Anthony, undated (Box 14)
        Candidate for General Treasurer, R.I.
      - Theodore, Nick, 1990 (Box 14)
        Candidate for Lt. Governor, S.C.
      - Vargas Llosa, Mario, 1990 (Box 14)
        Candidate for Presidency, Peru.
    - Pro Bono, Public Service and Nonprofit
      - Better World Society, 1990 (Box 14)
      - Chicago Zoo, 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 14)
      - Coalition Against Double Taxation, 1990 (Box 14)
      - Coalition for Free Television, undated (Box 14)
      - Energy Foundation, undated (Box 14)
      - Financial Services Council, 1991 (Box 15)
      - Humana Hospital (Louisville, Ky.), 1991 (Box 15)
      - National Resources Defense Council (NRDC), 1989, (3 folders) (Box 15)
      - Office of Economic Development, New York, N.Y., 1991 (Box 15)
      - President's Drug Advisory Council, 1990 and undated (Box 15)
      - United Nations High Commission on Refugees (UNHCR), 1991 (Box 15)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda Subseries, 1990-1993
    - Advertising-related, 1991 (Box 15)
    - John Lindsay Reunion Committee, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Letters of Congratulations to David McCall on Joining SMG, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Memoranda
      - General, 1991-1992, (4 folders) (Box 15)
      - Martin Sorrell (WPP) to David McCall, 1990 Mar. 12 (Box 16)
      - Relating to Sawyer family trip to Disneyland, 1991 (Box 16)
      - To Partners, 1992 (Box 16)
      - To Robert Teeter, on State of the Union, 1991 (Box 16)
      - To Tom Wicker (New York Times), 1990 Jun. 25 (Box 16)
- Hunter Fan Company Series, 1990-1994 and undated, (4 boxes)
  Consists primarily of reports pertaining to periodic meetings of the Board of Directors, of which McCall was a member. In addition there is information on marketing strategies and advertising campaigns. Arranged into four categories--Advertising, Board of Directors, Finance, and Memoranda--and alphabetically therein.
  - Advertising (Box 16)
    - Advertising campaign planning, 1994, (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Focus groups, 1994, (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Materials supporting advertising initiative, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Board of Directors (See also Oversize Materials, Oversize Box OV3.)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 16)
    - Directors' compensation, 1992-1993 (Box 16)
    - Expense reports relating to McCall's activities as Director, 1992 (Box 16)
    - Meeting, 1992 Aug. (Box 16)
    - Reports to the Board of Directors, 1992 Jan.-Feb., (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Reports to the Board of Directors, 1992 Mar.-Dec.; 1993 Jan., (11 folders) (Box 17)
    - Reports to the Board of Directors, 1993 Apr.-1994 Mar., (12 folders) (Box 18)
    - Reports to the Board of Directors, 1994 Apr.-July, (3 folders) (Box 19)
  - Finance
    - Actuarial Report, tax year ending 10/29/93, 1993 May (Box 19)
    - Audited financial statements for fiscal 1993, 1994 Jan. 28 (Box 19)
    - CCM Capital report, 1992 (Box 19)
    - Financial statements, 1990-1991 (Box 19)
    - FY-1992 financial plan and forecast, undated (Box 19)
    - FY-1993 budget, 1992 Oct. 23 (Box 19)
    - FY-1994 preliminary budget review, 1993 Sept. 1 (Box 19)
  - Memoranda, 1992-1994 (Box 19)
  - Notes from a meeting with Bob Beaseley and Ken Garvey, 1992 Feb. 4 (Box 19)
  - Printed materials, 1991, 1993 (Box 19)
- Shepardson, Stern & Kaminsky Series (SSK), 1993-1999 and undated, (1 box)
  Includes materials related to David McCall's work as Chairman of SSK, a public relations firm, from 1993-1999. The series primarily documents administrative and financial operations along with limited correspondence and internal office memoranda. Included are David McCall's 1995 letters to Michael Eisner and Senator Chris Dodd (then-Chairman of the Democratic National Committee), along with correspondence related to his pro-bono work with the Initiative on Tobacco Marketing to Kids, an advocacy group for Tobacco-Free Kids. The series is arranged into three categories--Administrative Files, Correspondence, and Financial Papers--and alphabetically therein.
  - Administrative Files (Box 20)
    - Brochures
      - Hawthorn Group, undated (Box 20)
      - Southern Company, 1996 (Box 20)
    - Corporate Code of Ethics policy, 1997 (Box 20)
    - International operations, 1998 and undated (Box 20)
    - Partners meetings, 1994-1996 (Box 20)
    - Personnel/Staffing, 1995-1999 (Box 20)
    - Planning and strategy, 1993-1996 (Box 20)
    - Reports
      - Branding Revisited, undated (Box 20)
      - Competitive Insights, Miriam Wohabe, 1999 Jan. (Box 20)
      - Core Capability, undated (Box 20)
  - Correspondence
    - Letters
      - To Senator Chris Dodd, 1995 Dec. (Box 20)
      - To Michael Eisner, 1995 Aug. (Box 20)
      - To the New York Times, 1995 Jan. 5 (Box 20)
    - Memoranda
      - Budget adjustments memoranda, 1995-1999 (Box 20)
      - General memoranda, 1994-1999 (Box 20)
    - Tobacco-Free Kids: initiative on tobacco marketing to kids, 1993-1996 (Box 20)
  - Financial Papers
    - Budgets
      - Balance sheets, 1993-1998, (3 folders) (Box 20)
      - Budget projections, 1993-1999 (Box 20)
    - Client profitability reports, 1996 and undated (Box 20)
    - Financial statements, 1993 Dec. (Box 20)
    - Tax projections, 1994-1995 (Box 20)
- Refugees International (RI) Series, 1991-1998 and undated, (3 boxes)
  Documents McCall's involvement with Refugees International, an independent non-governmental organization dedicated to international refugee aid work and advocacy, including his activities as both a Board member and an international aid worker. The bulk of the material relates to McCall's refugee aid and demining work in Africa, Cambodia and Thailand, and Yugoslavia/Bosnia, including several folders of travel itineraries and journals which describe his trips to these countries. The series is arranged in two subseries--Activities and Administrative--and alphabetically therein.
  - Activities Subseries, 1992-1998 and undated
    Bulk of the material relates to landmines and international demining campaigns, specifically in Africa and Cambodia. Included are two Superman comic books (DC Comics) that confront the dangers of landmines and advocate demining, and two letters addressed to ABC News anchors (Peter Jennings, Lynn Sherr) on child prostitution in Cambodia. Arranged alphabetically.
    - Africa (Box 20)
      - The Great Lakes Partnership idea, undated (Box 20)
      - Kenyan office summary, 1998 (Box 20)
      - London/Africa trip and itinerary, 1992 Apr.-May (Box 20)
      - Research and reports, 1992 (Box 20)
      - South Africa: Raphaely (Pauline Beatrice) will/bequest, 1998 (Box 20)
        Ms. Raphaely was a South African humanitarian activist who bequeathed money to RI for refugee assistance projects in South Africa.
    - Book project: Book of Refugees, 1993 (Box 20)
    - Cambodia/Thailand (See also Oversize Materials, Oversize Box OV3.)
      - Cambodian reports and recommendations, 1992 (Box 20)
      - Cambodia trips: notes and correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 21)
      - Child trafficking and prostitution
        - General, 1995 Aug. (Box 21)
        - Letter to Peter Jennings/ ABC News, 1995 Sept. (Box 21)
        - Letter to Lynn Sherr/ ABC News, 1995 Aug. (Box 21)
      - Thailand/Cambodia trip: travel and itineraries, 1992 Jan., Nov., (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Landmines
      - Africa mission
        - American Embassy in Maputo, Mozambique, 1997 Feb. (Box 21)
        - Mozambique: The Development of Indigenous Mine Action Capacities, 1997 Feb. (Box 21)
      - CARE, 1997-1998 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 21)
      - Demining Superman comics, 1996, 1998 (Box 21)
      - Halo Trust: Clearance of Anti-Personnel Minefields... 1998 Feb. (Box 21)
      - HUDISA: Advantages of Clearing Minefields... in Mozambique, 1998 Apr. (Box 21)
      - Humanitarian Demining
        - Equipment catalog: Taming the Demon, 1997 (Box 21)
        - Washington conference, 1998 May (Box 21)
      - Independent Demining Assessment Center (IDAC): concept paper, 1998 June 5, and undated, (2 folders) (Box 21)
      - Marshall Legacy Institute, 1998 (Box 21)
      - United Nations Association (UNA-US)
        - Africa trip, 1998 Apr. (Box 21)
        - Landmine clearance inspection tour, 1998 Apr.-May, (2 folders) (Box 21)
        - Mozambique mine information presentation, 1998 Apr. (Box 21)
        - UNDP Accelerated Demining Programme, 1997 Apr. (Box 21)
    - Yugoslavia/Bosnia
      - Bosnia, 1993 (Box 21)
      - Bosnia and Soros Fund, 1993 (Box 21)
      - Don't Let Sarajevo Die advertisement, 1993 Mar. (Box 21)
      - Letter to New York Times: Bosnia/Neville Chamberlain, 1995 Nov. (Box 21)
      - UNICEF and Bosnia Image and Message Evaluation, 1993 (Box 21)
  - Administrative Subseries, 1991-1998 and undated
    Includes materials related to the administrative and fund-raising operations of Refugees International, grant proposals, mailings and solicitations addressed to individual and corporate contributors, and several trip journals. The latter provide a detailed personal account of David McCall's aid work in Cambodia, Thailand, and Africa from 1992-1998. The subseries includes both handwritten drafts and printed/bound versions of these journals. Arranged alphabetically.
    - D.C. office: staff list, 1992 May (Box 22)
    - General correspondence, 1991-1993 (See also Oversize Materials, Oversize Box OV3.) (Box 22)
    - Grant proposal: Refugees Emergency Action Program, 1992
      - Ford Foundation (Box 22)
      - J.P. Morgan (Box 22)
    - Mailings and solicitations
      - Board members, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Contributions, 1992-1993 (Box 22)
      - General, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
      - Help the People Who Help the Kurds advertisement, 1991 (Box 22)
      - Leonard Mayhew, 1992-1993 (Box 22)
        Mayhew was president of Mayhew Communications, who performed fundraising for RI.
      - Refugees International brochure, undated (Box 22)
      - RI Bulletin (Iraq and South Asia), 1991-1992 (Box 22)
    - Meetings (Executive Committee/Board of Directors), 1992-1993, (5 folders) (Box 22)
    - Lionel Rosenblatt (President of RI)
      - Congressional statements and articles, 1991-1993 (Box 22)
      - Rosenblatt/McCall correspondence, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Trip journals
      - African drought, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Africa land mine mission, 1998, Apr.-May (Box 22)
      - Return to Cambodia, 1992 Nov. (Box 22)
      - Thailand/Cambodia, 1992 Jan.-1995 June, (4 folders) (Box 22)
- Speeches Series, 1958-1990 and undated, (3 boxes)
  Includes texts of speeches, talks, and commencement addresses given by McCall, along with a small collection of speeches given by others. There is also a set of speech files that contain clippings, writing fragments, and other materials used to compose or plan speeches. In a few cases, speeches are accompanied by supporting materials and relevant correspondence. The series is arranged into two subseries--Speeches by McCall and Speeches by Others. Speeches by McCall are organized into a number of topical categories--advertising, commencement addresses, social-political issues, testimonials, and speech file materials--and alphabetically therein. Speeches by Others are arranged alphabetically by author.
  - Speeches by McCall Subseries, 1958-1990 and undated (Box 23)
    - Advertising-Awards
      - 12th Annual EFFIE Awards, 1981 (Box 23)
      - Dentsu Awards, 1975 (Box 23)
      - Givers and Receivers of Awards..., ca. 1968 (Box 23)
      - The Great Award Caper, or The Lunatics Have Taken Over the Asylum, ca. 1969 (Box 23)
    - Advertising-Careers
      - And What Do You Do For a Living? 1965 (Box 23)
      - Boys' Club of New York, 1967 (Box 23)
      - Department of Journalism, University of Nevada, 1975 (Box 23)
      - Pace University's Breakfast with the Chief series, 1976 (Box 23)
      - What Can You Do for Advertising? 1962 (Box 23)
    - Advertising-Client Relations
      - Getting Your Money's Worth, 1986
        - Copy of speech (Box 23)
        - Correspondence (Box 23)
        - Supporting slides (Box 23)
      - How to Be a Great Client, 1967 (Box 23)
    - Advertising-Creativity
      - Advertising and Society: A New Creative Challenge, 1973 (Box 23)
      - The Grasshopper Myth, ca. 1970 (Box 23)
      - I vs. We: A Creative Dilemma, 1964 (Box 23)
      - The Joy of Advertising, 1988-1989
        - Copies of speech (See also Oversize Materials, Oversize Box OV3.), (2 folders) (Box 23)
        - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (See also Oversize Materials, Oversize Box OV3.) (Box 23)
      - The Joy of Retailing, 1978 (Box 23)
      - Magic, 1977 (Box 23)
      - Management's Hunt for Young Creative Talent, 1963 (Box 23)
      - The Many Faces of Print, 1978-1979
        - Copies of speech (See also Oversize Materials, Oversize Box OV3.) (Box 23)
        - Slides, (2 folders) (Box 23)
        - Supporting Materials (See also Oversize Materials, Oversize Box OV3.) (Box 23)
      - Schizophrenia: When the Pebble of Creativity Hits the Pond of Business, 1977 (Box 23)
      - The Soul of a Product, 1958 (Box 23)
    - Advertising-Industry Concerns
      - AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies) annual meeting, 1975 (Box 23)
      - Account Management and Great Advertising, 1978 (Box 23)
      - Corporate Communication, 1974 (Box 23)
      - David McCall-Edward Ney (Young & Rubicam) debate, 1981 (Box 23)
      - Dayton Advertising Club, 1979 (Box 23)
      - Effective message strategy, 1971 (Box 23)
      - Full-service advertising agencies, ca. 1971 (Box 23)
      - Is Print Advertising Dead? 1982 (Box 23)
      - Is the Advertising Trade Press Undermining The Industry It Serves? 1970 (Box 23)
      - The Last 25 Years in Advertising: Has Anything Changed? 1975 (Box 23)
      - New Management Needed, 1982, (2 folders) (Box 23)
      - Proprietary Association, 1968 (Box 23)
      - Retail Advertising: Gigantic and Growing, 1974 (Box 23)
      - Treasurers I Have Known, 1985 (Box 23)
      - What I believe About Advertising in Today's Market Environment, 1976 (Box 23)
      - What One Copy Writer Expects of a Product, 1963 (Box 23)
      - Who Should Run the Modern Advertising Agency? 1976 (Box 24)
    - Advertising- McCaffrey & McCall
      - About McCaffrey & McCall, ca. 1974 (Box 24)
      - Agency Staff Breakfast, 1976 (Box 24)
      - End-of-year speech to agency staff, 1971 (Box 24)
      - Taking McCaffrey & McCall private, undated (Box 24)
      - Western States Advertising Association, 1975 (Box 24)
    - Advertising-Research